In the latter half of the
Twentieth Century,
rapid advancements in technology
at last resulted
in the development of artificial
substitutes for human beings.
A synthesis of mechatronics, artificial
intelligence, and biotechnology,
they freed people from all
kinds of menial labor.
People called these symbols of the era,
"Boomers, assemblers of prosperity."
People all hold more love and dreams
than they can hold
with both hands,
and paint those dreams
for tomorrow
while entrusting the future to a
new-falling star.
If you go step by step
on your own two legs,
without stopping
before everything your arms
touch transforms into phantasms
you can approach those dreams.
Now begins the unending dream
when you search for yourself, sleeping
in the depths of your heart.
Now begins the unending journey.
Fix your sights on a faraway time.
Good night.
Hey, Bogarde, why don't you join us?
Cut that out, you jerk!
I beg your pardon, sir.
Under Article 0012 of the Regulations,
I cannot leave this area.
So long. Good night,
Bogarde.
Good night.
Take care, okay?
Mike, Ellie, good night.
This is a No-Parking Zone. Please
move your vehicle at once.
If you do not move within fifteen seconds,
the Police will be notified.
AD Police, AD Police,
this is Glory Ba...
A bank robbery involving powered
suits is in progress.
The scene is Glory Bank,
in the Kabuto Area.
All personnel, check
your equipment.
A bank robbery is in progress at
the Kabuto Area Glory Bank.
All personnel, check
your equipment.
You're completely surrounded! Come
out of those powered suits quietly!
I'll count to three! If you don't come out
by then, we're coming in after you!
One!
Two!
Three!
Fire! Fire!
Scatter! Run for it!
What the hell...
That's not one of
our choppers.
Which means...
Shit! Damage report! Where
are our choppers?!
No way those guys
were amateurs.
Please give us permission to assemble
a special mobile suit team!
We're up against an outfit with
some serious military suits!
With our current equipment, we're
just throwing our lives away!
Are you listening, Chief? The way things
are now, we can't do our job!
I know what you're saying, but
it just makes my life difficult!
Employing the heavy mobile force is an
extremely difficult decision to make
when you consider the potential
for civilian casualties, you know?
We know that! That's why we
need the Diet's approval.
Please meet with the Diet, so we can use
the heavy equipment without delay.
All right, all right...
But, complaints from citizens
have been heavy lately.
And that's something
we can't ignore.
It's your job as Special Police to find
some way to catch these criminals
without using the
heavy equipment.
Hold it!
Thank you, AD Police!
You, too, can be one of the elite! Join
AD Police, for youthful adventure!
AD Police now recruiting!
What is it with the
new Chief?
He's some corporate retiree they
appointed so he could earn
his retirement pay.
They think AD Police is a cash cow, after all.
That's ridiculous. He'll ruin the good
name of the Advanced Police.
Would you like a refill
on your coffee?
I tell you, AD Police's
future is shot.
Anyway, about that
bank robbery...
What's this?
I'm sorry. Oh, she's
done it again.
There's just no end to the breakdowns
on this built-in coffee-maker model.
I'll have someone clean
this up right away.
You're a real problem
for me, you are.
That reminds me, a hot dog I ate
recently had a spoon in it.
That's because even though they
look like human beings
they've got no more brains
than an orangutan.
Man, I tell ya, there's Boomers
everywhere.
It's the labor shortage.
I hear these cheap Boomers
are selling like hotcakes.
So will there eventually be nothing
but Boomers in Mega Tokyo?
We, AD Police, are the Special
Felony Crimes Elite Team
but almost all crime in this town
is connected with Boomers.
The Normal Police try to stick us
with writing tickets for them,
and the bureaucrats,
afraid of complaints
treat us like we're
a nuisance.
And to top it off, there's
this new Chief.
Would you prefer to try calling
on the Knight Sabers?
The Knight Sabers...You know, I haven't
heard anything about them lately.
What's going on
with them?
Those mercenaries?
Where might a person go
In search of streetlights
And lots of dreams?
Why won't time stop
itself for me
Just the way it is now?
The days when we laughed
side by side
Are all so far away
Catch me, oh, catch me.
I'm drifting away in
the dead of night.
Catch me...Warm
my closed heart
In the palm of your
hand, always.
Damn! The bigshots
all split.
Priss, babe! That was good! very good!
-Huh?
You were excellent, Priss.
But...
Oh, the big guys are always
busy with something,
but it seemed as though they really
wanted to hear the whole thing.
You mean...?
Uh-huh. Didn't I tell
you not to worry?
We can begin preparations for recording
as early as tomorrow.
Re...Recording? The...The pro
debut I've dreamed of?
Yes! Your songs will be
all over Mega Tokyo!
M...My songs...
My songs...?
Now that that's settled, let's continue this
discussion at my place, just you and I...
All right!
Pr...Priss!
My songs are gonna get recorded!
All right! All Right!
Here it comes!
Hey, Omni's going up! Does
someone have info on them?
Nene's tip about Omni's involvement
in developing a new AI was dead on!
Yes? Oh, Omni? Yes, I definitely
think it's going up.
Thirty? Why, certainly, sir.
I'm also buying Omni...so go up, go
up...and I'll never stop laughing!
It really was a good idea
for me to change jobs.
Is your Boomer peppy? If he's getting
run down, then he needs cyber-kun!
Super-power your Boomer. Revive
him instantly, with cyber-kun!
Hey, have you two been listening
to what I've been saying?
My songs...
Oh, Essex is on
the move...
Hey!
What is it, Nene? Want
another beer?
Don't you drink too much. If you strip
again, I won't be responsible for you.
Who's going to strip?
Strip? Did someone
say strip?
Who's going to strip?
Hey, this isn't the planned M&A!
I can't let them get away with it.
You're money-crazed.
You got some nerve talking about
me, Little Miss Cyberpunk.
You only hear me when
I'm insulting you.
What's so interesting about working
for a securities firm?
I'm making money with my brain now.
No more sweaty aerobics for me!
Say, Priss, when you get the money from
the sales of your CD, give it to me.
I'll double it for you.
Sounds awful...
All you two think about are yourselves!
Aren't you concerned about Sylia?
Sylia?
What about Sylia?
We apologize for the
inconvenience.
When did they start
building here?
Some time ago. You
didn't know?
No. And Sylia?
Nowhere to be found.
Hey, what're we
gonna do?
"What're we gonna do?"
About what?
About Sylia!
She's probably gone to
see Mackie, right?
Isn't he in Germany? He took off
to study there all of a sudden...
You two sure
are carefree.
If you're that worried,
look for her yourself.
You're in AD Police,
after all.
AD Police can't be relied upon!
That's why the Knight Sabers are necessary!
Let's go get those powered-suit
bank robbers!
I don't like such barbaric things.
For one thing, we won't get any money from it.
Plus, I can't get hurt
before my debut.
And you don't care what happens
to the Knight Sabers?
The Knight Sabers...I am kind
of nostalgic about them.
No...Nostalgic?
Those were good
times, huh?
Why do you refer to them
in the past tense?
Oh, I never thought that the Knight
Sabers would ever break up.
Last night, around 8:30 P.M., another
bank was assaulted
by a gang wearing military
mobile suits.
This incident occurred out in the open,
in the busy Fourth District
and by the time AD Police arrived, the
gang had vanished without a trace.
AD Police still have no leads as
to the gang's true identity.
Nevertheless, public outcry against AD
Police's unreliability is growing,
and speculation is that the organization
itself will be re-examined.
How AD Police got to
be like this will be...
How can you sit and watch that so
calmly? Aren't you insulted?
What's the point? We can't take
down mobile suits like those.
Don't you have any pride
in being AD Police?
Dying with your boots
on isn't very trendy.
Besides, you can't spend your
own insurance money.
You've got some
way with words.
Even the Police have gone
bad in this town!
Come on, Daley, let's go work off some
stress at the shooting range!
You'd better not.
I told you not to do it. The boss seems
to be in bed with a game-maker.
Damn!
Oh, it's you, Nene.
Hey! Are you gonna
kill me?
After I went to the trouble of digging up
the data on those powered suits?
It's a little off.
This is as close as they get. Perhaps
they've been modified.
The EC was developing a prototype suit
for close combat three years ago,
but when faults were identified during
the testing stage, development halted.
At least, officially.
Officially?
This is as far as the AD
Police Databank goes.
But there's probably more
to it, right, Nene?
How about a coupon good for three days'
worth of free desserts at Scirocco?
According to another source, there
is data which indicates
that a European mercenary outfit
employed this type of suit.
A mercenary outfit?
Which database did
you pull this from?
Neo-NATO's Top Secret Line.
There'd be an international incident
if anyone found out.
The illegal Army...South America,
the Middle East, Southeast Asia.
Why are such professional
warmongers
playing "Gangsters and Terrorists'
in Mega Tokyo?
I can't believe they're in
it just for the money.
But look!
Apparently their leader,
one Col. Lando,
was killed in action a year ago, in
an operation in the Philippines.
I remember that.
Word had it that a big Japanese concern
was backing a mercenary outfit.
But the operation
went awry,
and nearly the entire unit was
supposedly wiped out.
I'm beginning to get
the picture...
But we probably can't do
anything to stop them.
Don't give up! AD Police
is all there is now!
That's it, no doubt about it.
Well done, Col. Lando.
Yes, sir!
It does indeed appear to be one of
the components of the new AI.
But, by itself, it
is meaningless.
One of the last two components appears
to be at Zone Corporation Labs
but we do not know the
location of the other.
Get them, whatever it takes. This AI is
absolutely essential to our project.
Yes, sir!
Stop saluting, Lando.
I am not your commander anymore,
I am your comrade.
Okay...there you are...
Now I've got you!
Oh, what's the use? I can't rely on AD
Police, I can't get a hold of Sylia,
and I can't even
beat this game!
Hi!
Sylia!
Where've you been?
Here and there...Been renovating
the shop, too.
How are Priss
and Linna?
Oh, they're just peachy!
Let me tell you!
I'm currently staying nearby,
at the Imperial Hotel.
I wonder if you'd get the others and
come up to my room this evening.
I've something important to
discuss with all of you.
Some..Something important?
I'll have a feast laid
out for you.
Sylia...
What's with the
fancy food?
It's not normal, is it?
Maybe it's our
last supper!
What's wrong with you? Hurry up
and eat, so we can start our talk.
Sylia...about
this "talk"...
I won't be able to relax without at least
hearing what this talk is about.
Oh, me neither.
Oh...well, there's nothing
for it, I suppose...
I'd really wanted to discuss this after
dinner, in a leisurely fashion, but...
The truth is...
-No! I won't hear of us breaking up!
Calm down, Nene.
We understood from the outset that
this would happen someday.
But...But I like the work we
do as the Knight Sabers!
Uh, hold on a second,
would you?
You don't have to say another word,
Sylia. I'm already resigned to it.
If Priss and Linna quit,
I'll do it alone!
Hey, don't put it like that. Fact is, a
pro debut was always my dream...
...and I'm going to be busy
once it happens, but...
Yeah, me too. I can manage it, sure,
say, when the market's closed.
Sylia, I'm begging you!
Stop the Knight Sabers from breaking up!
I wondered what you were talking about!
Is that what you were thinking?
Then you're not going to
talk about breaking up?
No, we're not going to break
up, you silly girls!
Then, that something important...
Is the discussion of our
next job, of course.
An awful lot of offers have accumulated
during our brief vacation.
And since the equipment upgrades finally
seem to be finished as well...
...I thought it was time to start
up again...not break up!
Then all my worrying
was for nothing...
Nene!
What makes you think that the Knight
Sabers would disband, anyway?
Oh? Priss, your pro
debut is set, right?
Huh? Oh, uh, yeah...
Linna, you're working hard at your
securities firm, aren't you?
How about buying a
few shares, Sylia?
Let's talk about that later, when we have
more time. But right now, let's eat.
Don't mind if I do!
There seems little doubt that the bank
robbers currently plaguing the city...
...are the mercenary outfit known
as the illegal Army.
But the strange thing is, it's a matter of
record that their leader, Col. Lando...
...was killed some years ago, along with
nearly all his men, in a failed operation.
I found out this much just by using
AD Police's computers.
That's terrific, Nene.
Well, with you gone, and the Knight
Sabers seemingly breaking up...
...I figured that AD Police would have
to take our place, somehow.
Will you stop talking
about breaking up!
I'm sorry.
But, if we consider this data, then just
who is causing all the fuss now?
That's the question. Some members
might possibly have survived.
And they're trying
to take revenge...
...on the Japanese corporation
that sent them to destruction?
But all they've done
so far is rob banks.
That doesn't seem
to be the case.
The fact is, our client this time
out is Zone Corporation.
I know Zone...they make Boomer
brains. What's the connection?
This is one component of the special
AI which Zone Corporation...
...secretly developed for
a new type of Boomer.
Zone hasn't told the media, but the
illegals stole this component...
...from Glory Bank, together with
30 billion in gold bullion.
I've never seen
anything like it.
They can't announce anything because
of corporate security concerns.
Naturally, just the one component
is of no use by itself.
The AI's faculties can only be realized
if all four components are assembled.
So the first two were
at Glory and Omni?
Right. In short, they're using the
money as a smokescreen.
But their real objective is the
four components of this AI.
Our job is to protect
the remaining two.
But how?
The bait has already been laid out. We
may get a nibble any time now.
This makes three.
Hold it right there,
mercenaries!
Surrender! Resistance
is useless!
Not the flies again...
Throw down your
weapons at once!
Damn! Damn it!
You guys won't be pushing
anyone around anymore!
That idiot!
Let's do it!
A hornet among
the flies...
This is for the pride
of AD Police!
Don't interfere!
I'll take him.
Leon doesn't stand a chance
against a suit like that!
Let him do it his way.
This is the end!
Now!
Sorry 'bout that.
Not so fast!
Victory is mine.
Hang on! We're getting
out of here!
It's no use, sir!
Please, just leave me!
I won't let you die!
I'm gonna save you!
Welcome back
from the dead.
It's humiliating, but
he beat me.
You take it easy for a while.
I'll explain it to the Chief.
Putting that aside, why did they steal
a component of a research project?
It doesn't seem like they
were after money.
But it amounts to the same thing.
After all, they can convert it into money.
No, that's not Lando's style. He
must be after something else.
You are the warriors who
have been chosen...
...to bring forth a new order
upon the world.
This war you fight
is a holy war.
The world is changing. The history of
foolish old humankind is ending...
...and we, the chosen,
will purify the world!
What the hell is this?
Isn't it great? You'll look terrific
when you put it on!
Oh, and here's your
sheet music.
Huh? This ain't
my song.
Oh, that song will be a coupling
song and this is the main one.
It's by Fuyumoto, the popular idol
hitmaker, so it can't miss!
I...Idol?!
Like I said, leave everything to me,
and I won't steer you wrong.
Uh, well...
There's nothing to be
embarrassed about.
After all, we're already one
flesh, inseparable.
That does it! You got some nerve,
thinking I'll hold still for this!
There's no way I'll become an
idol, you son of a bitch!
Uh-huh...This is a temporary
thing, you see...
Huh? There's...no need to talk like
that...what? Sell out? Uh, yes...
What? You've lost 500,000? Just
like me, huh? Oh, nothing...
Omni's really taken
a nosedive.
It's because of that bank
robbery, isn't it?
Uh, yes, well, it's...Damn the illegal
Army! I've had it up to here!
Resignation
Sir!
Huh?
I resign, effective
immediately!
The illegal Army should presently be
heading for Stephan Laboratories...
...thanks to the false information
I've planted.
Knight Sabers are Go!
This is a dummy!
Shit! It's a trap!
Pull out!
We...we can't, sir! Our escape
route is completely sealed off!
No matter! We'll just
go up to the roof!
Knight Sabers...Go!
You can't just do as you
please in this town!
You've gotten a bit cocky,
haven't you?
Kill them!
How about you give me
the last component?
Ha! What can you do, alone?
When the battle is joined, nobody
stands in our way and lives!
You babes are
pretty good!
Priss, Nene, we'll attack him
from three sides, all at once!
Okay!
What the...?
Leave them to me!
Got 'em!
Without their suits, they're
just cheap Boomers.
Die!
Damn!
That's all for today,
Knight Sabers!
You don't get off
that easily!
What?!
Stealing the second generation Boomer
AI under cover of bank robberies...
...wasn't simply gathering funds
or taking revenge, was it?
Who's their boss?
Priss!
I am the illegal Army. I take
orders from no one!
Release her! You have no
hope of winning now!
I am a soldier of the glorious
illegal Army.
This isn't enough to
make me give up!
Shove it!
What?!
Take this!
Leave this to me!
Now!
Give yourself up! Who
is your boss?
A self-destruct device!
What?!
It's too late to start running now!
I'll destroy everything within 3km!
One minute to
detonation!
Find the self-destruct device!
Okay!
What's wrong with you? I'll
blow us all away together!
The illegal Army does
not surrender!
There it is!
Nene, link up with me!
Priss!
Synchronize targets, Priss!
Okay!
It's all yours, Priss!
If you miss, it's all over!
Shut up!
You're good...
you beat us...
...this time, that is...
What?!
I am a failed Boomer; neither
Boomer nor human.
But soon, there will come a world...with
neither humans nor Boomers in it...
...a dream world, controlled only
through chaos and terror...
...if anyone can make
it reality, he can...
I guess there's still hope
for this town, after all...
So what's become of
your pro debut?
I'm gonna write some decent
songs, and go for it again.
When the bell rings, showtime's over.
I got a call from another record
company just the other day.
Oh, I've also decided to work
at another securities firm!
Tonight, I've seen my dream's continuation.
Didn't you say you never even
wanted to see money again?
But it's lovely to watch
money pile up.
Today ends, having gone the way I wanted
You really are money-crazed.
I heard that, Little Miss Cyberpunk!
And tomorrow, I seek an easygoing dream.
What are you quarreling about?
Oh, Sylia, these two still haven't learned anything.
Nene!
People are dreaming hurriedly
Well, do your thing, but don't
forget the Knight Sabers.
and though no voice gets through,
strangely, I can hear your voice.
cool eyes, staring just that way
cloud the mirror of the heart
concealing one's true self.
With stardust reflected in your eyes
you embrace freedom
and firmly catch your own dream, now.
Showtime, in a town full of misunderstandings.
Tonight, the heart walks a tightrope.
Straining my eyes in the pitch darkness,
unable to see anything, I seek tomorrow.
The bustling town is dancing
with a seemingly secret heart, tonight.
The melody you and I heard is carried
on the wind, and surrounds you.
Sensitive cool eyes really know the things
that possess eyes which seem to melt ice.
With stardust reflected in your eyes
you embrace freedom
and firmly catch your own heart.
Sensitive cool eyes really know the things
that possess eyes which seem to melt ice.
With stardust reflected in your eyes
you embrace freedom
and firmly catch your own heart.